<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Angus Solitaire</string>
    <string name="ten">10</string>
    <string name="jack">Jack</string>
    <string name="queen">Queen</string>
    <string name="king">King</string>
    <string name="ace">Ace</string>
    <string name="howToPlay">How to Play Angus Solitaire</string>
    <string name="hintOne">The objective of the game is to score as many points as possible before
        the deck runs out of cards. Scores less than 75 points are not submitted to High Scores.</string>
    <string name="hintTwo">Press on the deck to draw a card. If the card drawn is a face card
        (10s are face cards),it will automatically go to its “Place”.
        If the card drawn is any other card it will automatically go to the Black or Red
        “Place” based on its color.</string>
    <string name="hintThree">The Black and Red “Places” can only contain one card at a time.
        For example, if a Black number card is drawn and there is already a card in the Black “Place”,
        you must either discard the drawn card or discard the card in the Black “Place”.</string>
    <string name="hintFour">To score points, the “Pile” must contain one face card of each suit
        (one club, one diamond, one spade, and one heart) based on the current level,
        starting with Jack. Points are not scored until a level is completed.
        Having a complete “Pile” will move you to next level.</string>
    <string name="hintFive">To “Collect” a face card into the “Pile”, you must have the following
        cards on the board (example shown above): The face card you want to “Collect” into the “Pile”,
        A number card that matches the suit of the face card in one of the color “Places”,
        and another number card of the opposing color in the other color “Place”.
        Once all of these cards are on the board, press the face card to “collect” it and
        move that card onto the pile. Face cards that can be “Collected” are surrounded with a red border.</string>
    <string name="hintSix">
        The sum of the number cards used to “Collect” a face card is put towards your “Pile” total.
        Once a level has been completed the face cards from that level become “Wild”. “Wild” face
        cards can be “Collected” instead of the current level’s face cards. “Wild” face cards which
        can be “Collected” are surrounded with a red border. “Wild” face cards have the same
        prerequisites as the current level face cards to be collected onto the pile. 10s start the
        game as “Wild”.</string>
    <string name="hintSeven">“Wild” face cards can also be used as number cards. To use a “Wild”
        face card as a number card, press on that card and it will move to it’s respective color
        “Place”. “Wild” face cards that can be used as number cards will be surrounded with a yellow
        border. Pressing a “Wild” face card will only move it to it’s respective color “Place” if
        that “Wild” face card cannot “Collected”.</string>
    <string name="hintEight">If you wish to skip the level you are currently on, press the “BREAK”
        button. Skipping a level will “break” the face cards of that level. You can only use the
        “BREAK” button once per game.</string>
    <string name="hintNine">Once a level has been “Broken”, the face cards from that level cannot be
        “Collected”. The face cards from the “Broken” level cannot be used as “Wild” face cards.</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="top_card_access">Top Card</string>
    <string name="pile">Pile</string>
    <string name="discard">Discard</string>
    <string name="clubs">\u2663</string>
    <string name="_8">8</string>
    <string name="diamond">\u2666</string>
    <string name="spade">\u2660</string>
    <string name="heart">\u2665</string>
    <string name="black">Black</string>
    <string name="press_to_discard">Press to Discard</string>
    <string name="red">Red</string>
    <string name="deck">Deck</string>
    <string name="_52">52</string>
    <string name="score">Score</string>
    <string name="_0">0</string>
    <string name="pileColon">Pile:</string>
    <string name="level">Level:</string>
    <string name="press_here_for_game_over">Press Here for Game Over</string>
    <string name="new_game">New Game</string>
    <string name="how_to_play">How to Play</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="scoreColon">Score:</string>
    <string name="breakString">break</string>
    <string name="press_to_draw">Press Card to Draw</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="high_scores">High Scores</string>
    <string name="rankColon">Rank: </string>
    <string name="average_game_score">Average Game Score: </string>

    <string name="highScore_board_id">CgkIvvHOjI4eEAIQDg</string>
    <string name="totalScore_board_id">CgkIvvHOjI4eEAIQDA</string>
    <string name="numOfGame_board_id">CgkIvvHOjI4eEAIQDQ</string>
    <string name="app_id">1034576705726</string>
    <string name="achievement_75_points">CgkIvvHOjI4eEAIQAA</string>
    <string name="achievement_100_points">CgkIvvHOjI4eEAIQAQ</string>
    <string name="achievement_150_points">CgkIvvHOjI4eEAIQAg</string>
    <string name="achievement_200_points">CgkIvvHOjI4eEAIQAw</string>
    <string name="achievement_300_points">CgkIvvHOjI4eEAIQBA</string>
    <string name="achievement_improbable">CgkIvvHOjI4eEAIQCw</string>
    <string name="achievement_jacks">CgkIvvHOjI4eEAIQBQ</string>
    <string name="achievement_queens">CgkIvvHOjI4eEAIQBg</string>
    <string name="achievement_kings">CgkIvvHOjI4eEAIQBw</string>
    <string name="achievement_aces">CgkIvvHOjI4eEAIQCA</string>
    <string name="achievement_break">CgkIvvHOjI4eEAIQCQ</string>
    <string name="achievement_well_played">CgkIvvHOjI4eEAIQCg</string>

    <string name="high_score">High Score</string>
    <string name="total_score">Total Score</string>
    <string name="number_of_games">Number of Games</string>
    <string name="average_game_pro_rank">Average Game (pro rank)</string>
    <string name="achievements">Achievements</string>
</resources>
