<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Angus Solitaire</string>
    <string name="ten">10</string>
    <string name="jack">Jack</string>
    <string name="queen">Queen</string>
    <string name="king">King</string>
    <string name="ace">Ace</string>
    <string name="howToPlay">How to Play Angus Solitaire</string>
    <string name="hintOneTitle">Game Objective</string>
    <string name="hintOne">The objective of the game is to score as many points as possible before
        the deck runs out of cards. Scores less than 75 points are not submitted to High Scores.</string>
    <string name="hintTwoTitle">Drawing Cards</string>
    <string name="hintTwo">Press on the deck to draw a card. If the card drawn is a face card
        (10s are face cards), it will automatically go to its Position.
        If the card drawn is any other card it will automatically go to the Black or Red
        Box based on its color.</string>
    <string name="hintThreeTitle">Red and Black Boxes</string>
    <string name="hintThree">The Black and Red boxes can only contain one card at a time.
        For example, if a Red number card is drawn but there is already a Red card in the Red Box,
        you must either discard the drawn Red number card or discard the card in the Red Box.</string>
    <string name="hintFourTitle">Scoring Points</string>
    <string name="hintFour">To score points, the Pile must contain one face card of each suit
        (one club, one diamond, one spade, and one heart) based on the current level,
        starting with Jack. Points are not scored until a level is completed.
        Having a complete Pile will move you to the next level.</string>
    <string name="hintFiveTitle">Collecting Face Cards</string>
    <string name="hintFive">To Collect a face card into the Pile, you must have the following
        cards on the board (example shown above): The face card you want to Collect into the Pile,
        a number card in one of the color Boxes which matches the suit of the face card,
        and another number card in the other color Box. Once all of these cards are on the board,
        press the face card in its position to Collect it and move that card onto the Pile.
        Face cards that can be Collected are surrounded with a dark border.
        The sum of the number cards used to Collect a face card is put towards your Pile total.</string>
    <string name="hintSixTitle">Wild Face Cards as Face Cards</string>
    <string name="hintSix">
        Once a level has been completed, the face cards from that level become Wild. Wild face
        cards can be Collected into the Pile instead of face cards of the current level. Wild face cards which
        can be Collected as face cards are surrounded with a dark border. Wild face cards have the same
        prerequisites as the current level face cards to be collected onto the pile. 10s start the
        game as Wild.</string>
    <string name="hintSevenTitle">Wild Face Cards as Number Cards</string>
    <string name="hintSeven">Wild face cards can also be used as number cards. To use a Wild
        face card as a number card, press on that card and it will move to its respective color
        Box. Wild face cards that can be used as number cards will be surrounded with a lighter
        border. Pressing a Wild face card will only move it to its respective color Box if
        that Wild face card cannot Collected into the Pile as a face card instead.</string>
    <string name="hintEightTitle">The BREAK Button</string>
    <string name="hintEight">If you wish to skip the level you are currently on, press the BREAK
        button. Skipping a level will break the face cards of that level. You can only use the
        BREAK button once per game.</string>
    <string name="hintNineTitle">Broken Level</string>
    <string name="hintNine">Once a level has been Broken, the face cards from that level cannot be
        Collected. The face cards from the Broken level cannot be used as Wild face cards.</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="top_card_access">Top Card</string>
    <string name="pile">Pile</string>
    <string name="discard">Discard</string>
    <string name="card_left">Cards Left:</string>
    <string name="cards_squandered">Gone:</string>
    <string name="clubs">\u2663</string>
    <string name="_8">8</string>
    <string name="diamond">\u2666</string>
    <string name="spade">\u2660</string>
    <string name="heart">\u2665</string>
    <string name="black">Black</string>
    <string name="press_to_discard">Discard</string>
    <string name="red">Red</string>
    <string name="deck">Deck</string>
    <string name="_52">52</string>
    <string name="score">Score</string>
    <string name="_0">0</string>
    <string name="pileColon">Pile:</string>
    <string name="level">Level:</string>
    <string name="press_here_for_game_over">Press Here for Game Over</string>
    <string name="new_game">New Game</string>
    <string name="how_to_play">How to Play</string>
    <string name="done">\u2713</string>
    <string name="scoreColon">Score:</string>
    <string name="breakString">break</string>
    <string name="press_to_draw">Draw</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="high_scores">High Scores</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>
    <string name="rankColon">Rank: </string>
    <string name="multiplier_colon">Multi: </string>
    <string name="average_game_score">Average Game Score: </string>
    <string name="card_size_ratio">6:7</string>

    <string name="high_score">High Score</string>
    <string name="total_score">Total Score</string>
    <string name="number_of_games">Number of Games</string>
    <string name="average_game_pro_rank">Average Game (pro rank)</string>
    <string name="achievements">Achievements</string>

    <!--Preferences Keys-->
    <string name="visual_preference_category_title">Visual Preferences</string>
    <string name="dark_theme_preference_key">dark_theme_preference_key</string>
    <string name="dark_mode_preference_title">Dark Mode (changing this will end current game)</string>

</resources>
